
const questAndAns = [ 
  {
    question: 'Who is the first to die in the fight against Vegeta and Napa?',
    answerChoices: ['Tien', 'Yamcha', 'Krillin', 'Piccolo'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yamcha'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who lives at Kame house?',
    answerChoices: ['Master Roshi', 'Kami', 'Bulma', 'Suprime Kai'],
    correctAnswer: 'Master Roshi'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who cut off Vegeta\'s tail?',
    answerChoices: ['Krillen', 'Yagerobi', 'Gohan', 'Goku'],
    correctAnswer: 'Yagerobi'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which dragon ball was called "Grandpa"?',
    answerChoices: ['1 star', '7 star', '5 star', '4 star'],
    correctAnswer: '4 star'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the turtle that lives at Kame House?',
    answerChoices: ['Turles', 'Tur Tur', 'Turtle', 'Gregory'],
    correctAnswer: 'Turtle'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Bulma\'s mothers name?',
    answerChoices: ['Scarf', 'Bra', 'Panty', 'Bikini'],
    correctAnswer: 'Bikini'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Goku afraid of?',
    answerChoices: ['Needles', 'Turtles', 'Losing', 'Buu'],
    correctAnswer: 'Needles'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the first to achieve super saiyan 2?',
    answerChoices: ['Goku', 'Vegeta', 'Gohan', 'Napa'],
    correctAnswer: 'Gohan'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Symbol doesn\'t ever appear on Gokus gi?',
    answerChoices: ['亀 Turtle Hermit', '神 Kami', '悟 Son Goku', '界王 King Kai'],
    correctAnswer: '神 Kami'
  },
  {
    question: "What is Goku's wife\'s name?",
    answerChoices: ['Cha Cha', 'Cho cha', 'Chi Chi', 'Chi Cha'],
    correctAnswer: 'Chi Chi'
  },
  {
    question: "How many times does Yamcha die (in the main DBZ timeline)?",
    answerChoices: ['5', '1', '4', '2'],
    correctAnswer: '2'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the best character in DBZ?',
    answerChoices: ['The Prince of all Saiyans', 'Vegeta', 'Vegeta IV', 'Bulma\'s man'],
    correctAnswer: 'trick'//trick question
  },
  {
    question: "How many dots are on Krillin\'s head?",
    answerChoices: ['6', '9', '8', '4'],
    correctAnswer: '6'
  },
  {
    question: "What is Android 17\'s real name?",
    answerChoices: ['Lambert', 'Lazuli', 'Limpit', 'Lapis'],
    correctAnswer: 'Lapis'
  },
  {
    question: "Who did Bulma have a crush on while on Namek?",
    answerChoices: ['Burter', 'Zarbon', 'Dadoria', 'Qui'],
    correctAnswer: 'Zarbon'
  },
  {
    question: "How many times has Goku used the spirit bomb in battle?",
    answerChoices: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
    correctAnswer: '3'
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the afterlife in DBZ?",
    answerChoices: ['Other World', 'Over World', 'Spirit World', 'Heaven'],
    correctAnswer: 'Other World'
  },
  {
    question: "Who has destroyed the moon?",
    answerChoices: ['Master Roshi', 'Buu', 'Goku', 'Freeza'],
    correctAnswer: 'Master Roshi'
  },
  {
    question: 'And now for something completely different:<br>Which is not a Magic: The Gathering keyworded ability?',
    answerChoices: ['Offering', 'Epic', 'Dash', 'Elevate'],
    correctAnswer: 'Elevate' 
  },
]